http://www.tradingscreen.com/legal-notices

Legal Notices
BY DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO TRADINGSCREEN®USING THIS SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, STORAGE AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BY TRADINGSCREEN® IN THE MANNER SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. For the purposes outlined above, we may send your information internationally. However, TradingScreen® will ensure that your information is treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Data Export Certain parts of this site are provided by or in conjunction with third parties. TradingScreen® is not responsible for the use of personal information which you give directly to such third parties, or which they may collect about you while you visit pages hosted by them. Please refer to their respective privacy policies for information about their use of personal information.
Third party hosting TradingScreen® will not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information about you collected through the Web Site to other parties, without your consent.
Privacy protection TradingScreen® also reserve the right to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement, or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority. TradingScreen® reserve the right to disclose your information in special cases, for example, when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), TradingScreen® title, rights, interests or property, or those of other web site users, or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.
Disclosure to third parties TradingScreen® may use personal information collected through the Web Site (a) to identify you as a representative of a registered corporate or institutional user; (b) to monitor the frequency of your use of the Web Site for our marketing purposes, and for internal administration and analysis; and (c) to send you additional and up to date information on TradingScreen® products and services. When TradingScreen® sends an e-mail update, it will include an instruction on how users may remove themselves from the e-mail list, or you may opt out of the opportunity to receive e-mails at any time by notifying TradingScreen® atsupport@TradingScreen.com.
Use of information TradingScreen® may also set and access TradingScreen® cookies on your computer. Cookies are used as identification to permit access into this Web Site in place of login and password and to track your movement from one area of the Web Site to another only.
We may also collect generic and statistical information about you and your usage of our Web Site using standard Web Site traffic analysis tools but we will only this data for internal marketing research. As part of your contacting or registration process with TradingScreen®, for the Web Site we may collect the following personal information about you:
* your name, your company name, your company’s country, your company or your personal address, e-mail address and phone number.
* as part of the Web Site registration process to access the password-protected area of the Web Site.
* if provided voluntarily by those who “Contact Us” (such as applicants for positions, potential customers, suppliers or interested parties) We only collect detailed personal information through the Web Site: Type of information collected.
Privacy Policy All other trade and service marks are the property of their registered owners. TradingScreen®, TradePrime®, TradePlus®, TradeSmart®, TradeExchange®, TradeAPI® are a registered service marks of TradingScreen Inc. The TradingScreen logo, TS TradeFIX, TS Trade Excel, TS TradeLink, and TS, are trademarks of TradingScreen® Inc.
Trademarks The Content may not be taken out of context or presented in an unfair, misleading or discriminating manner. You agree not to remove any copyright notice or other notice signifying TradingScreen’s®, any Provider’s or any third party’s intellectual property or other proprietary rights. Nothing contained on the Web Site shall be deemed or construed to confer any license or right, expressly, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, under any of TradingScreen’s®, any Provider’s or any third party’s intellectual property rights.
The works of authorship contained in the Web Site including, without limitation, all design, text and images are owned or used under license by TradingScreen®and are protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws. Such works may not be copied, reproduced, transmitted, displayed, performed, stored, distributed, used to create derivative works, altered, abridged or otherwise used in whole or in part without the prior written consent of TradingScreen® and/or its licensors, except for one temporary copy and one permanent copy to be used by you for personal, non-commercial use.
Copyright Some countries provide rights in addition to those above or do not allow the exclusion or limitation of implied warranties or liability for incidental or consequential damages. Therefore, the above limitations may not apply to you or there may be provisions which supersede the above. If any provision of these Legal Notices is determined to be invalid, superseded, illegal or unenforceable, in whole or in part, the validity, legality or enforceability of any of the remaining provisions or notices shall not in any way be affected or impaired thereby and shall continue in full force and effect. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless TradingScreen® and the Providers from any injury or loss (including reasonable attorneys fees) suffered, incurred or asserted as a result of (a) any misuse by you of the Web Site, including the Content, (b) any third party actions related to your receipt and use of the Content, whether authorized or unauthorized, and (c) any infringement by you of TradingScreen’s® and/or any Provider’s intellectual property rights. Neither TradingScreen® nor the Providers shall be liable for any loss or injury (including, without limitation, any loss or injury caused in whole or in part, by TradingScreen® or any Provider with respect to procuring, compiling, interpreting, editing, writing, reporting, delivering or transmitting any Content) in tort, contract, strict liability or otherwise to any user or third party except for liability arising out of gross negligence or willful misconduct. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, IN NO EVENT SHALL TRADINGSCREEN® OR ANY PROVIDER BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR LOST PROFITS, LOST OPPORTUNITY, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, EVEN IF TRADINGSCREEN® OR SUCH PROVIDER HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. The Web Site may contain (i) hyperlinks to web sites operated by persons other than TradingScreen® and (ii) message boards and chat rooms containing information and content submitted by persons other than TradingScreen® and the Providers. Such hyperlinks, message boards and chat rooms are provided for your reference and convenience only. You agree not to hold TradingScreen®or the Providers responsible for the content or operation of such portions of the web sites. A HYPERLINK DOES NOT AND SHOULD NOT BE DEEMED TO SUGGEST, IMPLY OR MEAN THAT TRADINGSCREEN® OR ANY PROVIDER IN ANY WAY ENDORSES OR SUPPORTS THE CONTENT, OPERATOR OR OWNER OF SUCH HYPERLINKED WEB SITES. TRADINGSCREEN® AND THE PROVIDERS HAVE NOT DEVELOPED OR REVIEWED THE CONTENT APPEARING IN OR ON SUCH HYPERLINKED WEB SITES OR ON ANY MESSAGE BOARD OR CHAT ROOM AND NEITHER TRADINGSCREEN®NOR ANY PROVIDER DOES OR SHOULD BE DEEMED TO IN ANY WAY ENDORSE OR SUPPORT ANY CONTENT THEREIN. You understand that the hyperlinked web sites, and the message boards and chat rooms may contain illegal or objectionable content or dangerous computer viruses. You assume, and TradingScreen® and the Providers hereby disclaim, all responsibility for any loss or injury sustained by you as a user of such hyperlinked web sites, message boards and chat rooms. The Content is obtained from Providers and is believed by TradingScreen® to be accurate and reliable. The Web Site, including the Content, includes facts, views, opinions and recommendations of individuals and organizations deemed of interest. Because of the possibility of delays and human and/or mechanical error, as well as other factors, neither TradingScreen® nor the Providers are or shall be responsible for any delays, interruptions, errors, inaccuracies or omissions in or on the Web Site, including the Content. EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED HEREIN, THE CONTENT AND THE WEB SITE ITSELF ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TRADINGSCREEN® AND THE PROVIDERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TRADINGSCREEN® AND THE PROVIDERS HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM WITH RESPECT TO THE WEB SITE, INCLUDING THE CONTENT, ANY AND ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED AND STATUTORY REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND TO YOU AND/OR ANY THIRD PARTY INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTY AS TO MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE, INCLUDING THE CONTENT, OR THE CORRECTNESS, QUALITY, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, PERFORMANCE, COMPLETENESS, TIMELINESS, OR CONTINUED AVAILABILITY OF THE WEB SITE, INCLUDING THE CONTENT. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER TRADINGSCREEN® NOR ANY PROVIDER MAKES ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY THAT THE WEB SITE, INCLUDING THE CONTENT, WILL CONFORM TO ANY DESCRIPTION THEREOF, BE FREE OF ERRORS, DEFECTS, VIRUSES OR OTHER CONTAMINATING OR DESTRUCTIVE ELEMENTS OR PERFORM ANY DESIRED OPERATIONS OR FUNCTIONS. TRADINGSCREEN® AND THE PROVIDERS DO NOT REPRESENT OR ENDORSE AND HEREBY DISCLAIM ANY OBLIGATION OR RESPONSIBILITY TO VERIFY THE CORRECTNESS, QUALITY, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, PERFORMANCE, COMPLETENESS, TIMELINESS, OR CONTINUED AVAILABILITY OF ANY OF THE CONTENT INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, PRODUCTS AND ADVERTISEMENTS, CONTAINED ON, DISTRIBUTED THROUGH OR LINKED, DOWNLOADED, OR ACCESSED FROM THE WEB SITE. You hereby acknowledge that any reliance upon any Content shall be at your sole and exclusive risk. TradingScreen® reserves the right (but shall have no obligation) to make improvements and complete, correct or update any delays, errors, inaccuracies or omissions in any portion of the Web Site, including the Content. Neither TradingScreen® Inc and its affiliates, nor their respective officers, directors, employees, secondees, vendors, suppliers and agents (collectively “TradingScreen®”), nor any of TradingScreen’s® third party information providers (the “Providers”) recommends, endorses, advocates or sponsors any of the securities, commodities or investments appearing on the Web Site, including in the Content. You acknowledge the risks associated with foreign exchange and other securities and commodities markets and trading transactions. TRADINGSCREEN® IS NOT AN AUTHORIZED FINANCIAL ADVISOR OR REPRESENTATIVE AND DOES NOT GIVE TAX, EMPLOYMENT OR INVESTMENT ADVICE. Any price information, quotes, forecasts, return estimates or indications of past performance are for information purposes only and do not guarantee future performance and do not constitute an offer to buy or sell or any solicitation of an offer to buy or sell any securities, investments or other property. The Web Site, including the Content, shall not serve as the primary basis for any of your investment decisions and neither TradingScreen® nor any of the Providers shall be or be deemed to be your financial advisor or fiduciary. TRADINGSCREEN® STRONGLY ADVISES THAT YOU OBTAIN ADVICE AND ASSISTANCE FROM A SECURITIES, COMMODITIES OR FINANCIAL SERVICES PROFESSIONAL AS APPROPRIATE, REGARDING THE EVALUATION OF ANY SPECIFIC INDEX, REPORT, RESEARCH, FORECAST, OPINION, ADVICE, DATA OR OTHER CONTENT.
Disclaimers The terms of the Notices are governed by the laws of the state of New York, without regard to the conflict-of-laws rules thereof. The terms of the Notices may be amended, modified or supplemented at any time by TradingScreen®. Your continued access to and use of the Web Site, including the Content shall be deemed to constitute your acceptance of any such amendments, modifications or supplements. TradingScreen® reserves the right to amend or supplement these Notices at any time. Please be advised that your use of the TradingScreen® web site (the “Web Site”) is subject to the limitations set forth below. By using the Web Site and the information and content contained on, distributed through or linked, downloaded or accessed from the Web Site (“Content”), you agree to the following limitations. You should read these Legal Notices (“Notices”) before accessing or using this Web Site, including the Content.
back to top
See Ultimate Trading Performance for Yourself
Request a demo
New York
TRADINGSCREEN inc. (HQ) 1 Penn Plaza 49th Floor New York, NY 10119
Tel: +1(212) 359 4100 Fax: +1(212) 228 0552
London
TRADINGSCREEN (UK) Limited 5th Floor, York House 23 Kingsway London, WC2B 6UJ
Tel: +44(0) 207 149 3100 Fax: +44(0) 207 149 3191
Paris
TRADINGSCREEN (UK) Limited 42 avenue Montaigne 75008 Paris France
Tel: +33 1 53 32 29 90 Support: +33 1 53 32 29 99
Frankfurt
TRADINGSCREEN (UK) Limited Frankfurt Zeil 127 60313 Frankfurt am Main, Germany
TRADINGSCREEN Hong Kong Limited 702, Dina House 11 Duddell St, Central, Hong Kong
Tel: +852 3192 7533 Fax: +852 2522 8771
Singapore
TRADINGSCREEN Pte. Ltd 10 Collyer Quay #24-06/07 Ocean Financial Centre Singapore 049315
Tel: +65-6486-7980 Fax: +65-6634-0075
Tokyo
TRADINGSCREEN Japan K.K. Orchid Place Roppongi, 6th Floor 2-2-8 Roppongi, Minato-ku Tokyo, 106-0032, Japan
Tel: +81-(0) 3-6704-4333 (ENG) +81-(0) 3-6704-4334 (JPN) Fax: +81 (0) 3 3586 2079
